The first lady gunfighter.
Hannie Caulder is a drama, western, crime film directed by Burt Kennedy.
After she's raped by the outlaw trio who murdered her husband, a frontierswoman hires a
bounty hunter to instruct her in the ways of a gun in order to exact her revenge.
Hannie Caulder, played by Raquel Welch.
Thomas Luther Price, played by Robert Culp.
Emmett Clemens, played by Ernest Borgnine.
Frank Clemens, played by Jack Elam.
Rufus Clemens, played by Strother Martin.
Bailey, played by Christopher Lee.
Hannie Caulder is a 1971 British Western film directed by Burt Kennedy and
starring Raquel Welch, Robert Culp, and Ernest Borgnine.
Kennedy called it a film " which a lot of people hate and a lot of people love.
We made it for a million dollars in forty days—and it was pretty good."
The film explores themes of gunslinger, bounty hunter, mexico, rape, texas.
The tone is emotional.